

Address Karachi, Pakistan

Contact +92 341 2445322 aliuzair999@gmail.com aliuzaircss@gmail.com

PROFILE

With a blend of artistry and technical prowess, I live to transform visions into visually stunning and highly functional applications.

With my expertise in the MERN stack, I am equipped to tackle any web development challenge with finesse.

EDUCATION

2018 - 2022

Institute of Business ManagementBachelor of Business Administration

2015 - 2017 **Tabani's College** HSSC Commerce BIEK

2013 - 2015 **Ghulaman-e-Abbas School** SSC Humanities AKU-EB

TECHNOLOGIES

- ✓ JavaScript
- ✓ React
- ✓ React Native
- ✓ Firebase
- ✓ CURRENTLY LEARNING
- ✓ Node js
- ✓ Mongo DB
- ✓ Express

LANGUAGES

Ali

Uzair

WWW

http://resume-ali.netlify.app/

Github

http://github.com/AliUzair999

Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/ali-uzair

Skype

join.skype.com/invite/xfqtcMBd3fGT

EXPERIENCE

2022 - 2023

CRESCENT SOLUTIONS

Offshore Operations Teamlead

2020 - 2021

HIQAIN

Telesales Account Manager

2019

SYBRID PVT LTD

Telesales Representative

CERTIFICATION

• MERN Stack

Enrolled in Expertizo University in web and mobile application development course. The modules cover HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, React Native, Mongo, Express, and Node.

WEB DEVELOPMENT

Course from SMIT in web designing and Android development. The module covers the core concepts of web and mobile application development using relevant technologies.

• ENGLISH ACCESS MICROSCHOLARSHIP PROGRAM

by U.S Embassy Islamabad. English Language Course conducted by iEARN Pakistan.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

VS Code
Github
Android Studio
OOOOO

